you rumbles rumbles and rumbles yes
ты тарахтит тарахтит и тарахтит да что ж
what is it
такое
Greetings from Ukraine the city of Khmelnitsky
Привет из Украины город Хмельницкий
where is
откуда
your channel from What is the name of your channel
Как у вас канал называется
For what purpose are you interested in
С какой целью интересует вот интересно
yellow-black for what purpose are
желто-блакидные с какой целью интересует
you interested in I'm interested But ask further
мне интересно Но интересуйся дальше
there is no
нет нет
money
денег
for some reason all Russian blocks are afraid
почему-то все русские блоки боятся
to be afraid Why
бояться Почему
Let’s turn off the war in Ukraine,
Давайте войну в Украине
I’m listening
выключил я слушаю
Why don’t you go to the military registration and enlistment office If you
Почему вы не идете в военкомат Если вы
If you support the war in Ukraine,
Если вы поддержите войну в Украине
look Let’s why Say you
смотрите Давайте почему Скажите вы
support the war in Ukraine and don’t go to the
поддержите войну в Украине а не идете
military registration and enlistment office you can’t ask me questions,
военкомат ты мне вопросы не можешь
I’m watching I can even
задавать могу я смотрю Я могу даже
number your who here  such a Denchik, this is
численно кто вот такой Денчик это
interesting. I love which bloggers are
интересно Я люблю которых блогеров
awesome, he wants to be short, he wants to fight
офигенный он хочет короче хочет воевать
for the Motherland, and who were you or something
за Родину а кто ты был что ли отправлять
?  we all know all these for
так как мы вот все знают все эти за
patriots who want to support
патриоты которые хотят поддерживают
support the war in Ukraine, so they
поддерживают войну в Украине так они
are still me  I’ll go when there is time
все-таки я вот пойду когда будет время
then the time will come it’s time it’s time
тогда придут время пришло время пришло
Why are you all sitting here and
Почему вы все вот эти рулетки сидите и
pile on
наваливайте
why Russian Why are you afraid Are you
почему русского Почему вы боитесь
afraid to go to the military registration and enlistment office they send you to the
Боитесь пойти в военкомат вас отправляют
neighbor You want to send
они соседа Вы хотите чтобы отправили
some neighbor
какого-то соседа
from work
с работы
If you are such a Denchik Type cool type  Yes,
Если ты такой Денчик Типа крутой типа да
some kind of shooting
каких-то стрельба
When you swear, this is an indicator
Вы когда матюкаетесь это индикатор того
that you burn out
что вы подгораешь
when Why don’t you go,
когда Почему вы не идете
you support the war in Ukraine
вы ж поддержите войну в Украине
turned off again a bunch of these z-patriots
выключил опять куча вот этих z-патриотов
Let’s not turn off the sound for you I
Давайте не выключил я вам звук Я вас
listen to
слушаю
music
музыку
so here Come on Why are you such a mess
так вот Давайте Почему вы такие конченые
weaklings
слабаки
Don’t turn off
Не выключайте
such propagandists they sit in
такие пропагандисты они сидят в
chat roulette and pile on like there
чат-рулетке да наваливают типа там
Khokhlov is shorter there he will merge now
Хохлов короче там он сейчас сольётся
it
сливается
just merges Yes they are all for war for war they
просто Да они все за войну за войну они
go out to chase Khokhlov there but
выходят чтобы там погнать Хохлов но
when it hits there are no answers And
когда попадает начинается нет ответов А
why why don’t you go he doesn’t  hears,
почему почему ты не идешь он не слышит
we understand that none of these Z
мы понимаем что ни один из этих Z
Patriots will go to the
Патриотов не пойдет не пойдет в
draft board, they all want Vasya from
военкомат они все хотят чтобы Васю с
work to  they sent it like they want it to
работы до послали типа они хотят чтобы
be sent by some friend there but not
этого послали какую-то там друга но не
them that's why everyone who listens he
они поэтому все кто слушает он сейчас
turned on the phone now
включил телефон
and we make
а мы делаем
good content because we have to
хороший контент потому что мы должны
show all these clowns like
показывать вот этих всех клоунов типа
and
и
we will make the sound shorter here he
мы будем делать звук короче вот он сам
turned off the sound see
отключил звук видите
he turns off himself
он сам отключается
[music]
[музыка]
cook the right things for people so
варим правильные вещи для людей так вот
all these Z patriots they
все вот эти Z патриоты они
don't want
не хотят
[music]
[музыка]
all these Z patriots they want
все эти Z патриоты они хотят чтобы вели
someone else to join the army but not him I was already
в армию кого-то другого но не он Я уже
at the shooting ranges was not there because
был на стрельбищах не было потому что
These are all such daredevils, they are
Вот все вот такие смельчаки они
for real When it comes to protecting
по-настоящему Когда встает дело защищать
Mother Russia, they disappear
Россию матушку они куда-то пропадают они
somewhere, they disappear somewhere, and here they can
куда-то пропадает и вот они могут там
do something there DJ glasses for themselves, but then
что-то там диджей очки себе да Но дальше
they are not enough, they want to send
их не хватает они хотят чтобы отправили
Vasya Petya well  And the second question. We
Васю Петю хорошо И второй вопрос Мы
owe all these patriots the main one.
должны вот этих всех патриота главный
So we sausage this one
Так мы за колбасили этого
[music]
[музыка]
he is already afraid because the
он уже боится потому что отправили
military registration and enlistment office sent
военкомат
his data to
его данные
this Denchik, we need to find
этого Денчика надо найти
now in Russia there is a huge
сейчас в России есть огромнейшее
amount  these Z Patriots who
количество вот этих Z Патриотов которые
want a withdrawal to something they don’t take the
хотят вывод на их что-то не берут
military registration and enlistment office, so who is watching us and who
военкомат поэтому кто нас смотрит да кто
knows this clown Write in the
знает этого клоуна Напишите в комментах
comments some E highlight yes the coordinates
его какие-то Э подсветите да координаты
that he is Who is he like that Because there are
что он Кто он так Потому что есть там
his dens there or what the channel is called  Yes,
его денчики или как канал называется Да
I saw I collect these Sicons base, we will find out the
видел Я этих сиконов базу собираю узнаем
last name Yes, we will find out the patronymic the city
фамилию Да узнаем отчество город
lives, we will send it to the draft board, this is how
проживает отправим в военкомат я вот как
I do it, look, come in at all if
делаю смотрите заходите вообще если у
you have some kind of ass Patriot in the city,
вас есть какой-то зад Патриот в городе
you know look
знаете смотри Заходите в военкомат там
you are not from Ukraine
не со своего Если вы не из Украины
call the recruiting office give the address the address of
звоните военкомат даете адрес адрес
this frame I so-and-so want
этого кадра Я такой-то такой-то хочу
to join the army so mobilize We have
пойти в армию так мобилизироваться У нас
a desire Volunteers bring him a
есть желание Добровольцев ему приносят
summons later Like so and these clowns they are
потом повестку Типа так и эти клоуны они
brave until they
смелые до того момента пока к ним не
knock on the door  when they didn’t knock
постучали в дверь когда им не постучали
on the door and don’t call them into the army, this
в дверь и не вызывает их в армию этот
very effective method is so because
очень действенный метод так потому что
Our task is to send all these ass Patriots
Наша задача всех вот этих зад Патриотов
to the front  if they hear
отправить на фронт если они слышат
Let's if you turned on the sound Let's in
Давайте если вы включили звук Давайте по
my opinion I hear I hear you you hear
моему я слышу я слышу вас вы слышите
me
меня
so look Why are you not in the army
так вот смотрите Почему вы не в армии я
I talked to my viewers
вот общался со своими зрителями
Why
Почему
are you not in the army I don't want to talk I don't
вы не в армии Я не хочу говорить Я не
want our troops to
хочу чтобы Наши войска
capture Moscow  You want people
захватывали Москву Вы хотите чтобы люди
from Russia to go
из России ехали их
all they didn’t say when you
все что не говорил не вы когда включили
turned it on turned off the sound to me
выключили мне звук
The fact is that
Дело в том что
we will try
мы постараемся
to invite
было приглашение
someone to donate there you see on the
киньте там кого-то донаты вы видите на
stream the person tries not to turn off the
стриме человек старается не выключил я
sound I listen to you I listen to you I listen to you
звук Слушаю тебя слушаю тебя слушаю еще
still  just show something that's still there for now
еще раз покажи что-то что там еще пока
throw Donat because the
киньте Донат потому что
yellow blocks came out on Well show
вылезла желтые блоки на Ну покажи
something well show Well baby Well what
что-нибудь ну покажи Ну малыш Ну что
is it
такое
What happened to you
Что с тобой случилось
I will call the video like an intellectual and the
Я так и назову ролик типа интеллигент и
channel And you will be redneck
канал А вы будете [__]
this channel
этот канал
you in general  subscribed to me not subscribed
ты вообще подписан на меня не подписан
why not subscribed yet
почему еще не подписалось
You can go see
Можете зайти посмотреть
people throw a pancake to the poor kid Donat he
люди киньте блин бедному пацику Донат он
is trying so hard to save his face and he didn’t
так старается короче сохранить лицо и не
succeed with
получилось у него
donations  why
донатики Да по-любому
now I’m recording now I’m recording
сейчас я сейчас записываю Я записываю
then I’m doing it so I show you know how the
потом делаю так показываю знаете как
zoo is like
зоопарк такой
Yes, what’s the name of the channel Andrey popykh I
Да как канал называется Андрей попых я
said Here’s my last name Andrey popyk
сказал Вот моя фамилия Андрей попык
navel or something Andrey
пупок что ли Андрей
fainted if your level is that you’re even
обморок если твой уровень что ты вообще
with a finger that this happened what we are for
с пальцем что это случилось то что мы на
Show now you want to cut yourself off now you want to cut yourself off
Покажи ты сейчас хочешь срезаться ты
on some things
сейчас хочешь срезаться на какие-то вещи
Because you feel yourself
Потому что ты себя ощущаешь
you need to somehow translate to this
тебе надо как-то перевести на вот этом
hands you have nails there a nozzle garlic
руки у тебя ногти там соплятор чеснок
level of intelligence in order to joke
уровня интеллекта для того чтобы шутить
as the
качестве
most interesting
Самое интересное
Why What do you have everything there  Why,
Почему Что у тебя там всё Почему
if you support the war against
если ты поддерживаешь войну против
Ukraine You must run in the forefront of the
Украины Ты должен бежать в первых рядах
navel You must run in the forefront
пупок Ты должен бежать в первых рядах
listens even hear I listen even
слушает даже слышу Я тебя слушаю даже
does not want to listen Listening to you Well, just
слушать не хочет Слушая тебя Ну просто
look at the nonsense, for example, in the zoo when I
бред смотри например в зоопарке когда я
come
прихожу
I want
Я хочу
a monkey with people there  then barks
с людьми там обезьянка что-то гавкает
Come on beaver
Давай бобер
[laughter]
[смех]
Hello This channel is called Rural Denchik If I'm not mistaken
Привет Это канал Если не ошибаюсь
Yes guy
называется сельский Денчик Да парень у
I have such a base of these
меня есть такая база этих
Russia  Russian bloggers Yes, I’m watching who’s there
россиянских блогеров Да Смотрю Кто там
How he communicates with people This is a
Как общается с людьми Вот это
typical Russian Russian cattle
типичная Российская [__] россиянское
so he sits there He’s something there
так он там сидит Он там что-то там
Ukrainians are being loaded something went wrong
украинцев нагружают что-то пошло не так
True Yes Denchik Yes when So
Правда Да что Денчик Да когда Значит на
Nutella was poured on you, it’s something wrong
тебя вылили нутеллу она что-то не
sweet It turned out Yes, I wanted to
сладкое Получилось Да хотел
load the Ukrainian
нагрузить хохла
something went wrong,
что-то пошло не так
he is shorter, he needs to
он короче ему надо как-то для своих
somehow leave somehow beautifully for his viewers
зрителей как-то красиво уйти
level of
уровень
jokes first class a
шуток первый класс
person can’t even somehow
человек даже не может как-то качественно
pin up a quality pin up, but they
подколоть качественно подколоть но они
all run away And pick up on one  moment
все убегают И подбирают на одном моменте
Yes, why are you all supporting the Z
Да почему вы все поддерживающие Z
operation supporting the war in Ukraine,
операцию поддерживающие войну в Украине
or whatever you call a special military
или как вы назвать специальную военную
operation Why don’t you run in the
операцию Почему вы не бежите в первых
forefront of the military registration and enlistment offices That is, you have been PR for 7 months
рядах военкоматы То есть вы 7 месяцев
or how
или сколько
much on this yes yes You need to
пиарились на этом да да Надо надо там
protect Russia mother Khokhlov to bring down a
защищать России матушку Хохлов валить
foreign
чужую страну
country  to your contracted
отправляли до ваших там контрактников
sources there And now it starts to heat up
источников А теперь начинает нагревать
your neighbors Yes, and you are silent, you
ваших соседей Да и вы молчите вы
begin to support further, that is,
начинаете поддерживать дальше то есть
receive  instead of going
получается вы вместо того чтобы идти
yourself, wait, don’t take you, I’m waiting for the
самим подождите не берите вас я жду
operation. In short, let’s go
операцию Я короче давайте меня
to the shooting range, I wasn’t in the mood,
был на стрельбище не было настроение
why seconds, that’s why
почему секунд вот поэтому
Our task is everyone who listens to us from
Наша задача все кто нас слушает из
Russia, yes, you have bloggers like that in the
России да у вас вот есть такие там эти в
cities Yes, there are
городах блогеры Да есть
there  there are also all sorts of
там инстаграмах также всякие просто там
neighbors on instagram who are all drowning for the
соседи которые вот все они топят за
operation, you need to help them rilaten there to the
операцию надо помочь им рилатень туда на
front because they so dreamed of fighting
фронт потому что они так мечтали воевать
with Ukraine in another country So
с Украиной в другой стране Так вот
look, go google the military registration and enlistment office of
смотрите заходите гуглите военкомат
your city
своего города
call
звоните
imagine there I am such and such such and such her
представляете там я такой-то такой-то ее
surnames like this Please write down we are
фамилии так Запишите пожалуйста мы
given to work I need to go to work I
данный на работу мне надо на работу Мне
brought a summons Yes, because I ca
принесли повестку Да потому что так я не
n’t do it myself There must be some reason
могу сам должны быть какие-то основания
Why bring it Bring it to work
Почему приносит Пусть приносит на работу
give coordinates candles Let the
даете координаты подсвечики Пусть
Patriots be taken away cool we need to help
Патриотов забирают круто надо помочь
people realize their dream they are here
людям реализовать их мечту они вот такие
everyone is so brave on the Internet so reality
все смелые в интернете так реальность
when the door is knocking is not worth
когда стучится двери не стоит
crap it's like this guy on the
обосранными это как вот этот Парниша
body  there will be
телеграм-канала там весь не будет
no communists there at all.
кто попытался мы их в первую очередь
we process it this way, I collect information and
обрабатываем так собираю информацию и
help the military enlistment office to
помогаю систематизировать военкоматом
systematize their data so that they
ихние данные так для того чтобы они
quickly
побыстрее
realize their dream, the dream of their life.
реализовали свою мечту мечту своей жизни
Therefore, if you have any information,
Поэтому если иметь какую-то информацию
send me a sender, you can write in the
присылайте мне присылайтером можете в
comments Write here or in a telegram If you
комменты Писать тут или в телеграме Если
do not want to be posted there Facebook You can
не хотите шиться там Facebook Можете
write Yes  we must help to
написать Да в личку мы должны помогать
help all of them as soon as possible to
помогать всем им чем быстрее
mobilize the chat roulette battalion we
мобилизировать чат рулетный батальон
will make
сделаем
Losev be the first on the list so he will be the
Лосев будет первый в списке так он будет
musical troops will go In short
музыкальных войсках будет идти Короче
here
тут
then it is Dima From Mariupol like yes
потом это Дима С Мариуполя типа да
who is
который
coming to Grishchenko yet we will
грядим на Грищенко еще вот Грищенко мы
press Grishchenko 1 and I think so with him  problems to the
дожмем 1 и думаю так у него проблем к о
fact that he is not quite more like a Russian
том что он не совсем скорее русский
passport Yes p  we got it shorter or
паспорт Да получил мы его короче или
deported how the Ukrainians will easily take it
депортирует как украинцы легко возьмут
as
как
a mobile, you need to help
мобика такого надо помогать
just getting aesthetic pleasure
просто получая эстетическое наслаждение
from helping the Russian army with the
от того что помогаю российской армии
Russian military registration and enlistment office to staff the
российским военкоматом укомплектовывать
mobilization plan with a blogger I believe
мобилизационный план блогером Я считаю
that every Z propagandist should be in the
что каждый Z пропагандон должен быть в
forefront, so help
первых рядах поэтому помогайте
move
двигаемся дальше украинцы
on  your veil is not there, we still
будь то на завеску ваши нету мы еще
YouTube it happens
YouTube бывает
It’s the right speech and the swell and the
Это правильный речи и пропуху и дуже
right arches to
правильные дуги
put in focus under the video and
задонать в фокусе под видео и посылания
send to donate prefer wallpaper on
на донат предпочтите обоевского на
Telegram a
Telegram
small deserted backside and rear frame It happens
малой пустынный зад и тыл раме Бывает
even in YouTube
и в YouTube
information and write your comments
информация и напишите свои комментарии
[music]
[музыка]
I’m a
я
project
проект
the antonian military enlistment office
антонские военкомат
will come up with him we can
придумает ему можем
[music]
[музыка]
at the front from the Zhiguna so Process Glory to
на фронте от жигуны Так Процесс Слава
Ukraine
Украине